# Jordan Da Graca

Web Design & Development



#### Introduction

Hi, I'm Jordan. I'm passionate about web design and development, and fresh out of my postgraduate studies, I'm looking to apply my learnings in a development environment with particular stringent focus on front-end web development. As a firm champion of creative thinking, I idealise creative problem solving to create functional, modern web applications in accordance with modern guidelines.

What initially started as a hobby quickly became a future career prospect as I undertook four years of university to obtain a postgraduate degree in the subject area.

### **Education**

**MSc Digital Design - Solent University**Graduated With Distinction
2019 - 2022

Bsc (Hons) Digital Design & Web Development - Solent University

Graduated With Honours 2022 - 2023

### **Contact**

07585259237 | dagracajordan @gmail.com

### **Proficiencies**

- HTML5	
- CSS3	
- Javascript	
- SEO	
- SCSS	
- NodeJS	
- Express / EJS	
- React	
- Figma	
- Wordpress	
- Adobe Suite	
- SQLite3	
- Python	
- NextJS	

### References

Character references available on request

### **Portfolio**

<u>jordandg.info</u>

## **Work History**

**Junior Web Support Technician - Damteq**Jan 2024 - Present

**Web Developer - Winchester Film Festival** Jan 2017 - October 2018